<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>https://longj724.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://longj724.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Snippet Note Taking Application - React, Node, MongoDB</title>
      <link>https://longj724.github.io/projects/codenote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://longj724.github.io/projects/codenote/</guid>
      <description>I utilized the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS) to create a basic note-taking application where users can embed snippets of code into their notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libary Notifier - React, Flask, sqlite</title>
      <link>https://longj724.github.io/projects/librarynotifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://longj724.github.io/projects/librarynotifier/</guid>
      <description>An application that sends me a text when a book from my local library is off of the waitlist. The frontend serves as an interface for me to search my library for books and add them to a SQL database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://longj724.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://longj724.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Justin Long, a junior at the University of Michigan. I currently live in Ann Arbor, but grew up and went to high school in a suburb of Cleveland, Ohio. I am studying computer science, and am also interested in entrepreneurship and psychology. Outside of school, I am very passionate about running and endurance sports.
Recent Events and What I&amp;rsquo;m Doing Now I spent last summer interning at Adatasol, a small SaaS company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Contribution: Gitpay - React, Node</title>
      <link>https://longj724.github.io/projects/gitpay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://longj724.github.io/projects/gitpay/</guid>
      <description>Gitpay
I utilized React and Redux to create a client-side form, and NodeJS and Express to receive the form inputs and send them to the correct recipients in an email. I also used JSON Web Tokens to create secure routes that only the receivers of the email could access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Cycle - Node, HTML, CSS</title>
      <link>https://longj724.github.io/projects/runcyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://longj724.github.io/projects/runcyle/</guid>
      <description>Deployed Here -&amp;gt; Run Cycle
This was one of the first side projects that I deployed to the web. I utilized NodeJS for the backend and Javascript, HTML, and CSS for the frontend. Users can enter in a starting location and distance that they want to run, and the application maps out a route for them that will return to the starting location.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>